<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="category_parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="category_hill_stations">Hill Stations</string>
    <string name="category_temples">Temples</string>
    <string name="category_water_parks">Water Parks</string>
    <string name="rishikesh">Rishikesh</string>
    <string name="rishikesh_description">Situated along the convergence of Ganga and Chandrabhaga, Rishikesh on the foothills of Himalayas is the hub of many ancient temples, popular cafes, yoga ashrams and adventure sports.</string>
    <string name="nainital">Nainital</string>
    <string name="nainital_description">Nainital with its beautiful lakes, temples and exotic scenery around is the perfect honeymoon paradise nestled in the arms of Kumaon Hills.</string>
    <string name="mussorie">Mussorie</string>
    <string name="mussorie_description">Situated at an altitude of 6000 ft., Mussoorie is a popular hill station famous for its colonial heritage and its religious sites.</string>
    <string name="badrinath">Badrinath</string>
    <string name="badrinath_description">Badrinath is a pilgrim centre (among one of the Char Dham) set in the backdrop of Neelkanth Mountain Peak dedicated to Lord Vishnu.</string>
    <string name="haridwar">Haridwar</string>
    <string name="haridwar_description">Situated along the holy Ganges, Haridwar is famous for its temples and ghats where pilgrims bathe to relieve themselves of their sins.</string>
    <string name="jimcorbet">Jim Corbet National Park</string>
    <string name="jimcorbet_description">Corbett National Park, set amidst the foothills of Himalayas, houses a variety of flora and fauna including rare ones such as tigers and is a treat for wildlife enthusiasts and photographers.</string>
    <string name="kedarnath">Kedarnath</string>
    <string name="kedarnath_description">Atop 3584 mts, this in one of the Char Dhams and thus one of the holiest pilgrim centres in the lap of Garhwali Himalayas.</string>
    <string name="yamunotri">Yamunotri</string>
    <string name="yamunotri_description">Revered as the origin of Yamuna river, the pilgrim centre (among one of the \'Chhota Char Dham\') nestled in the laps of Garhwal Himalayas at 3293 mts high lies close to the Indo-Chinese border.</string>
    <string name="gangotri">Gangotri</string>
    <string name="gangotri_description">This pilgrimage destination situated in Uttarkashi is one of the Chhota Char Dham.</string>
    <string name="auli">Auli</string>
    <string name="auli_description">Dotted with apple orchards, oaks and deodars; Auli is a popular hill resort in the Himalayan range dating back to 8th Century AD.</string>
    <string name="almora">Almora</string>
    <string name="almora_description">Cradled in the wilderness of Himalayan ranges, the sprawling town of Almora shaped like a horse-shoe is a hill station located in Uttarakhand that boasts of a pre-British heritage.</string>
    <string name="dhanaulti">Dhanaulti</string>
    <string name="dhanaulti_description">With Chamba and Mussoorie in proximity, this little town in Uttarakhand is an offbeat destination located at a height of about 2200 meters above sea level.</string>
    <string name="valley">Valley Of Flowers</string>
    <string name="valley_description">Valley of flowers, discovered in 1931 is a World Heritage Site for its wild untamed blooms surrounded by white peaks.</string>
    <string name="lansdowne">Lansdowne</string>
    <string name="lansdowne_description">Lansdowne at an altitude of 1,706 mt on a hillock is famous for its pristine Himalayan beauty, oak and pine forests, snow-covered peaks and lovely fresh air.</string>
    <string name="bhimtal">Bhimtal</string>
    <string name="bhimtal_description">Rested at a height of 1370m above the sea level, Bhimtal is spotted with temples lying amid the verdant mountains and a pristine blue lake.</string>
    <string name="rajaji">Rajaji National Park</string>
    <string name="rajaji_description">Encompassing the Shivalik mountain ranges, Rajaji National Park is abundantly rich in flora and fauna and proves to be a great holiday destination for nature lovers and wildlife enthusiasts alike.</string>
    <string name="nandadevi">Nandadevi National Park</string>
    <string name="nandadevi_description">In proximity to Nanda Devi, which is the second highest peak in India, lies the Nanda Devi National Park in the Chamoli district of Uttarakhand. A UNESCO World Heritage Site, this park is one of the most biodiverse regions in the world and is home to some of the rarest and unique high-altitude flora.</string>
</resources>
